Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/iqbal-miaha71192126 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C#

Node.js

Executive Search

Iqbal Miah

Principal Consultant (Software Engineering - UK, Europe, and Benelux) at Signify

London, England, United Kingdom

Summary

I specialise in providing Tech talent solutions for the UK and Europe. Having built trusted relationships within the technology community over the course of 7+ years, I've developed a deep understanding of the sector and the challenges of implementing solutions. So, I am well-placed to offer advice and support to all project leaders.

Alongside connecting candidates to the best career opportunities I help to develop their skills by providing access to online training and certifications. Not only does this help to raise the quality of the channel, but gives confidence to project leaders by ensuring that they always have the most experienced people on their programmes.

Working across multiple verticals, I have experience of recruiting the following professionals into both permanent and contract positions: CTO's, Engineering Managers, Software Engineers, Programme Managers, Practice Leaders, Change Managers, Project Managers, Business Analysts, Technical and Functional Consultants, and DevOps/Cloud Engineers.

Experience

Signify Technology
Principal Consultant
May 2024 - Present (1 year 2 months)

With over 8 years experience in the industry, proposing effective talent solutions are my specallisty. If you're looking for a new role, or looking to procure a talent solution to achieve your goals, we can help!

Types of roles I hire/source for (Software Engineer, Engineering SLT, DevOps Engineers, Data Engineers, AI/ML Engineers, and Project Managers).

Key areas:

- UK
- Benelux (Netherlands, Belgium, and Luxemburg)
- EU

Alternatively, if you're thinking about a hiring strategy between 1-30 hires, we can talk through a hiring strategy for cotingent Internal/External hires (Permanent/Contractors), SoW and project based solutions. Drop me a message or email me to book in a call - iqbal.miah@signify-tech.com

Explore Group

3 years 9 months

Team Lead

March 2022 - May 2024 (2 years 3 months)

London, England, United Kingdom

Senior Consultant

August 2021 - March 2022 (8 months)

London, England, United Kingdom

Technology Consultant

September 2020 - August 2021 (1 year)

London, England, United Kingdom

Specialising in frontend, backend, data and digital transformation projects, sourcing talent in the UK tech market.

Areas of expertise:

- React, Javascript, Typescript
- React Native and Mobile
- Node
- Ruby-on-rails
- Java
- .NET, Azure
- QA

For more information reach out for a confidential conversation - iqbal.miah@exploreltd.com

Cognitive Group | Recruiting For Your Future Senior Consultant - Azure, Cloud and DevOps contract February 2018 - August 2020 (2 years 7 months)

London, United Kingdom

Experts in talent acquisition. We build teams and nurture careers within Microsoft cloud, business applications, automation and Al. Join 100's of organisations and 1000's of professionals who have found each other through Cognitive. Global coverage, local knowledge.

Build your team with confidence:

We have over 10 years' experience building teams and supporting organisations in their transformation journeys. Our aim is to give you the freedom to run your business the way you want, by connecting you with top talent that fits your organisation. So, if you're looking to hire or build out your team, trust the Microsoft talent specialists. We can help with:

- Executive Search
- · Team acquisition
- · Experienced hires
- Diverse hires
- Cross training
- Flexible project workforce
- Specialist industry talent
- Talent pool analysis by Geography

Typical roles we recruit for within Azure, Infrastructure, Applications, Data, Al, Dynamics, Bl and PowerApps:

Partner, Senior Partner, Consulting Director, Business Change, Project
Director/Manager, Data & BI Architects, Solution Architects, Technical
Architects, Test Managers/Leads/Analysts, Tech/Functional Consultants,
Business Analyst, CRM/ERP Trainers, Infrastructure/Integration Architects,
Software Engineer/Developer, Azure Developer, .NET Developer, Full Stack
Developer, Azure Engineer, DevOps Engineer

Nigel Frank International Consultant July 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 8 months) London, United Kingdom

Microsoft Business Intelligence & SQL Consultant - Contract

Microsoft Business Intelligence Consultant specialising in placing contract MS BI, Analytics and Data Visualisation professionals across London. Our contract professionals are experts in their respective fields covering the MS Business Intelligence stack (SSIS, SSAS, SSRS) SQL Server, Data Analysis, Power BI, QlikView and Tableau across a variety of roles including:

- Solutions/Technical Architects
- Developers
- SQL DBA's
- Data Analyst's
- Business Analyst's
- Data Visualisation (Power BI, QlikView and Tableau)

Education

University of Westminster
Bachelor's Degree, Business Management · (2013 - 2016)